{"data":[{"question":"When George ________ this afternoon, he ________ his friends.","a":"will come \/ will bring","b":"comes \/ will bring","c":"comes \/ brings","d":"will come \/ brings","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Future tense\/simple present tense + while\/when + simple present tense.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"The Andersons ________ into their new apartment last week.","a":"moves","b":"move","c":"moved","d":"has moved","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Use the Simple Past to express the idea that an action started and finished at a specific time in the past (last week).\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"As I ________ the street, two cars ________ by me at full speed yesterday.","a":"crossed \/ raced","b":"crossed \/ was racing","c":"crossed \/ had raced","d":"crossed \/ were racing","answer":"4","explain":"\n- When\/As + Simple past tense, simple past continuous\/past perfect tense (this case is simple past continuous).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"Mr. Brink ________ the Atlantic by the time the news reaches him.","a":"cross","b":"are crossing","c":"will be crossing","d":"crosses","answer":"3","explain":"\n- By the time\/when + simple present tense , simple future continuous","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"If we ________ the news sooner, we would have written to John.","a":"received","b":"had received","c":"receive","d":"will receive","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Conditional sentence type 3: If + past perfect, would\/could\/should + have + PP.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"I'm sure they ________ Ellen the information if they had it.","a":"give","b":"will give","c":"gave","d":"would give","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Conditional sentence type 2: If + simple past tense, would\/could\/should + Verb.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"If a policeman ________ an accident, he will take the driver's name.","a":"see","b":"will see","c":"would see","d":"sees","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Condition type I: If + simple present, simple future tense\/simple present tense.\u00a0\n- Subject (a policeman) is singular.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"We are going to buy the furniture if we ________ some money.","a":"borrow","b":"borrowed","c":"will borrow","d":"would borrow","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Condition type I: If + simple present, simple future tense\/simple present tense.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"What ________ tomorrow if you ________ a millionaire?","a":"are you going to do \/ are","b":"were you doing to do \/ was","c":"will you do \/ was","d":"would you do \/ were","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Conditional sentence type 2: If + simple past tense, would\/could\/should + Verb.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"If Carl ________ so careless, he wouldn't lose his good job.","a":"wasn't","b":"weren't","c":"hadn't been","d":"wouldn't be","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Conditional sentence type 2: If + simple past tense, would\/could\/should + Verb.\u00a0\n- \u00a0To be - were (whatever the subject is singular or plural).\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"}]}